Thank you for watching!
Subtitler Iris Candy
Subtitler Iris Candie
Subtitler Iris Candy.
Subtitler Iris Candie.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
The morning chime has rung. We are Ichigaku, the club that wants to know.
Before we begin our program, we would like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for your favorite 1 and 2.
The person who has the number card with that number written on it is the MC.
Let's start voting!
I messed this up. I was watching.
Oh, really?
Which one is it?
Which is it?
It's not enough.
I think they match.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Fighting!
Okay, number two.
Okay.Seino.
You're happy. Yes, I am. That's why
So, Ema-chan, who is holding the number 2 ticket, is today's MC. I look forward to working with you.
I'm Sakurai Emma, and I'll be your MC today. Nice to meet you.
I am Yuna Nakamura. Nice to meet you.
Yes, I'm Yuna Nakamura.
Let's begin.
Ebichu's
Yukari de Fufuna Showroom
Yay!
Thank you for visiting the 61st Yukari De Fukuna Showroom of EBICHU today.
Ebichu's Yukari De Fufufuna Showroom is the sister show of our sister showroom, Uka's Showroom.
You can get an original avatar by signing up for our showroom,
You can get it by gifting it to us either for free or for a fee.
How about today?
There are a lot of people here today.
There are a lot of people here.
Thank you very much.
So here is the time to spread the word!
In order for as many people as possible to see this distribution,
I'm going to extend it on the official X of Ebichu now,
Please spread the word.
What pose are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
I want to make a M.I.A. pose.
I wonder.
I'll think about it.
I'll think about it later.
Thank you very much.
So, today's project is titled..,So, today's project is entitled,
A funny and funny survey talk.
I said it together.
I was happy.
It was reassuring.
Before I give a talk, I take a questionnaire and decide what I am going to talk about. That is what a survey talk is.
Now I will announce the theme of today's talk.
Here it is.
Number 1. After-school health care roll-hyper.
Number 2. At Jam Extracts also 2023.
Number 3. Waking up live.
No.4. Sakurayama's first solo live.
Happy Birthday.
Thank you very much.
Number 5. Meat.
Number 6. Cheese ball.
No. 7. Sprouts.
We only talk about food.
Yes, I do. So this time, I would like to take a survey from these 7 items.
Let's start the voting!
I would like you to vote at the live show.
Yes, I would like you to vote at the live show.
Otherwise, we will only talk about food.
Yes, I agree. By all means.
Yes, by all means.
Hey, it says that the second half is the menu.
That's right.
By all means, a live performance would be nice.
Yes, by all means. Please do it live.
Yes, please. You also had the Asora live concert.Yes, I am. Cherry, you also had Asora Live.
So you are looking back.
How do you feel about it?
Yes, I am.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Yes.
I'm a little nervous.
Don't worry, it's number 4.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine. You were fine, weren't you?
It's Emma Sakurai's heart solo show.
Yay!
Yay.
That's right. This is the first solo live of Emma Sakurai's birthday, Honey Emile Everyday, on September 13.
I went.
Yes, I did.
What was your most honest impression?
It was fun,
But I was more nervous.
That's exactly what it was,
I was more nervous than nervous,
I had a script, and I had to say a lot of things before the live performance,
There was a script,
There was a script, and it had a lot of kanji characters written in it.
I was very nervous, and normally I could read it,
I was very nervous, and there was a kana character called "jonai," which I could normally read.
I read it as "banai" with all my might,
Can you really read it in normal circumstances?
Really?
Really?Really?
Can you read it on a regular basis?
Yes, I can read.
It's just that I'm nervous,
In advance? I couldn't read that one,
I didn't understand that one,
I didn't know about that one, but there were things like that,
And then there were various songs.
From the very old songs of Ebitu,
to recent songs,
I have sung a variety of songs, from the very old songs of Ebichu
I had the opportunity to sing a variety of songs,
Above all, I was so happy to see only honey orange penlights for the first time,
I was so moved when I saw the view with only honey-orange penlights for the first time,
I was really moved.
Thank you so much to everyone who came.
It was a great experience.
Mr. Nakamura came, too,
But I had to work before that,
I was afraid I might not be able to make it.
But he dashed to the venue.
I ran the most. Life.
That's right. You don't have to run that much.
Because when Emma started to throw up,
I hugged her like, "This is it,
I was sweating more than you.
That's right.
When did you come to play a role in the show?
When we entered the venue,
Missing Geppo was playing,Because the Missingeppo was playing,
Before the marigolds?
I see.
I looked over and saw Yuna, and I was like, "Oh! I was like, "Oh my God!
She was smiling so much. I was so happy.
I was so happy that she was still there after the show, which made me feel relieved.
Thank you very much.
I was so happy. How was everyone?
It was fun, wasn't it?
I'm glad.
Please tell me that hug is far away.
Say it's the sweat of youth.
The sweat of youth.
You look really happy.
Yes, I am.
The previous Kizuna.
Her outfit was cute, too. With the hair band.
Yes, it was. They made the hair band in the image of this one,
There were lots of sparkles on the skirt and on the top,
But when I saw them on stage, they were so sparkly.
But when I saw it on stage, it was really sparkling.
When I was at the foot of the stage, my feet were shaking.
It was amazing. Smoke?
It was pooled under the stage,
I haven't seen that at many of your regular shows, and it was the first time I saw it,
I thought it was amazing.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
At a time of binary progress.
Binary progress.
We were able to get it out.
It was amazing.
It says I heard Yuna-chan's voice.
Yes. It was something like, when my eyes met Ema's, ha! I said, "I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That's it,
You heard her voice?
She said she heard it.
What?
That's what happened. And she was talking,
Oh, no. When she made eye contact with me, she fell silent for a moment,
My, ha! I heard my "Ha!
echoed. Wow! Was it Yuna's loud voice or the family's good hearing?
It's amazing. Yes, I think her voice was loud. But...
It's amazing that it was Moroki's voice. You found me! That's how I felt.
It was amazing. I was very grateful. Thank you so much. It was fun.
Next year, too.
I wish I could see it from the beginning next year. Please come.
I knew I was being too loud. You can hear me? It's a little embarrassing, isn't it?
I can't hear you, you know.
"Did you give her a present?" I did.
What did you give him?
Ema-chan told me that when she doesn't get enough sleep, her dark circles tend to appear,
She was worried about it,
She said she didn't have any concealer, so I gave her a good concealer.
Thank you very much.
It's really good.
Really? It's good.Really? Good.
It was really easy to use, thank you very much.
I did feel like there were fewer bears than usual.
I forgot.
Thank you very much.
Good. There doesn't seem to be any.
Good.
I'm still having bear problems, too.
As much as possible.
I'm going to sleep.
It doesn't go away even if I sleep.
Bears, you know. It won't go away.
I tried really hard to ask my mother. I asked my mother.
How do bears disappear?
She said, "Bears, you know. They don't disappear.
It made me sad.
I was told that too.
Maimi told me that the bear will never disappear even if I grow up.
Let's go to bed.
Yes, I will.
I know it's a bit far from what I wanted to talk about, but...
It was great.
Thank you very much.
So, that's it,
Shall we move on to the next topic?
Okay.
Okay, let's start the survey!
Start voting!
Start!
Ai! Ai!Ai! Ai!
What's up with that? But, you know, we've had quite a few live weeks,
It went on, didn't it?
On the contrary, recently, from April to the end of August, there was something happening almost every week. So, recently, we have been looking for the next live concert or something like that.
So I've been preparing for the next live concert by taking lessons and so on,
I feel really lonely because I don't have a live concert every week.
I understand.
It is sad, isn't it?
We used to do something every week.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Ai.
Five!
Five. Which one is it?
This is a topic we'd like to discuss alone.
We were just together.
We went to the Musicnik for the year.
It was great!
Um...
This was also the yakiniku party for the year's work...
I was born on the day of my birth, right?
What do you want to eat now?
Oh, no. What do you want to eat as a reward for your birthday? When I asked you.
You said yakiniku.
That's what I said, so today was also a reward for that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
But it was delicious.
We really ate a lot.
I mean, we had about three M.I.U. showrooms, right?
And the best part of the M.I.U. showroom isAnd the best part of the M.I.U. showroom is
Going out for dinner before the showroom.
The other day we had mentaiko tsukemei.
We had it, and even then
We were talking about how we wanted a reward for working hard for another month or so, and it turned out to be yakiniku.
It turned out to be yakiniku!
It was delicious!
Please tell me about the Yakiniku Settlement.
Yakiniku settee...
What's the first thing to start with?
Kalbi.
Albi kalbi.
I had the aburi kalbi sauce.
I had the negi shio tan.
And I had some thin meat.
And bulgogi.
I also had bulgogi
Tasty bulgogi!
Oh, it was delicious!
And I had green peppers.
And what else?
Cheese ball!
I also had cheese takkarbi and cheese balls!
And...
Oh, let's see...
Puldak pokmyeon!
I don't want to put it in.
I had buldak pokkmyeon!
I had pokkmyeon!
It was spicy!I'm sorry.
No, it really was.
I'm a spicy person.
I was a bad est.
But after spending more time with Yuna.
I became able to eat mokotan noodles.
I don't know if it's good or bad.
I started to be able to eat it.
That's why that puldak pokmyeon
It's all messed up!
Pull dak pokmyeon.
I was wondering if I could eat
I thought I could eat it.
I heard it was really spicy.
I tried it.
My throat was on fire.
Fire in my throat
It was really spicy.
It was good.
But it was good.
The worst thing you can do when you eat spicy food is to drink water.
The worst thing you can do when eating spicy food is to drink water during the process.
That was a no-no.
Once you drink water, it gets even spicier.
Why is that?
I don't know.
I don't know why.
It was always young Street.
Young?Young?
I'm young, because I eat ribs first.
First ribs? Are you young?
I don't know.
Young?
Because they're greasy.
The net gets dirty.
That's right.
I did have the net changed after it got dirty.
But I didn't cook a single piece of meat after that.
I wonder if it was a good idea to have it changed.
I don't know...
The flames are amazing.
The flame goes up so high.
I couldn't get it to go away.
I was like, "What should I do?
And Yuna, too.
And Yuna was like, "Oh my God!
Emma thought she had to do it.
She tried to put the net on, but it wouldn't go out.
But it didn't go away.
Does it work?
I don't know, but she did it.
Suddenly it just went "click, click, click.
Then I crushed the fire, but Yuni said...
She said crushing the fire doesn't make it go out.
It came out really well.
I've never grilled meat by myself.
I always had my mom or dad do it for me.I always had my dad or mom do it for me.
This is my first time baking.
Was it good?
Yeah, it was good.
It was good.
They put ice on it.
Oh, yeah.
Let's do it sometime.
Let's do it.
I didn't see anything like that.
Did they come when you asked them to?
That's for sure.
But it was amazing even before the appointment.
That's right. It was strong.
It was maxed out,
And before the meat arrived, they lit the fire the moment we sat down,
It was fast.
It burned for about 10 minutes until the first meat arrived.
It was hot.
I ate too much and my stomach was amazing.
He asked us to start with the charcoal salt.
Everyone said "Charcoal salt, Charcoal salt.
Why?
It was the last charcoal salt, right?
It was the last charcoal salt, wasn't it?
Because it was the last one because it was so sour.
It was the best.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
When you eat spicy food, you should drink milk or yogurt.He says that when you eat spicy food, you should drink milk or yogurt.
What do you think?
I don't like milk,
I've had it before,
But it is true that when I eat very spicy food,
When I feel like I'm in trouble, I drink yogurt first,
I heard that drinking yogurt is good for the stomach,
It's good for the stomach.
That's right.
But if you drink water, it becomes spicy.
It was hard. It was really bad.
But it was delicious.
I also ate shootball,
There was a Korean fair going on.
I wanted to go to that.
I also had fried dumplings.
I ate so much.
It was delicious.
But if the ema had been in front of the puldak pokkmyeon, one or two bites would have been no good,
I was impressed that he ate it even though it was spicy.
You were impressed?
How does one become able to eat spicy food?
I don't know, but I haven't eaten much lately, so I'm a little weak and frustrated.
Seriously?
I went to Fierce Tiger Ramen Nakamoto for the first time in a while,
Normally I would have eaten double the amount of Hokkyoku or something before,
But since I hadn't been there for a while, I was a little scared,
But I was a little scared because I hadn't been there for a long time, so I decided to go for the Hokkyoku and it was spicy.It was hard when I made it to the North Pole.
Kind of like muscle training?
Yes, it is.
My dad made shichimi (seven spice) for me.
There's a kerolina leipa called Dragon Breath, which is the hottest kerolina leipa in the world,
My father got shichimi that is hotter than that from somewhere,
I eat it.
You eat it?
Yes, I eat it with shichimi.
That's amazing.
But it's too spicy if you put too much.
No, it's spicy even if you don't put too much.
That's amazing.
Your father is really in another dimension. Spiciness.
But you know what, I can eat as well as my father now.
What should we do? Gentlemen.
What should we do?
What should I do?
What are we going to do?
That's great.
Thank you.
But you know, everyone in the Nakamura family likes spicy food.
No, just me and my dad like it.
Why can't your mother and the others?
I don't know, now that I can eat spicy food,
Now my mom and dad can eat spicy food,
My mom can eat very spicy food,
But my dad can't eat spicy food,
But if he can't eat such things as Moke Turmeric, then I don't know,
But, you know, I was able to eat it,But, you know, I was able to feed myself,
I wanted to feed him,
Recently, when I ate a lot of spicy food,
You should try some. I told her, "You should try some,
I force him to eat it even though he says he doesn't like it,
I enjoy her reaction when she says it's spicy.
But lately, I've been doing that to my mom too much,
But lately, I've been doing it to my mom so much that she gets angry when I tell her to try it because it's really not spicy,
She gets angry when I tell her to try it because it's not really spicy.
I know, right?
It's spicy anyway.
She doesn't believe me anymore.
They don't believe me.
Okay. Well, I'll leave it here.
Okay.
One more.
Yes, one more.
Let's have one more.
Okay, let's start voting.
Bakun.
Ai.
I wonder.
I wonder what it is.
I wonder what's next.
There's so much to choose from.
Hey.
Yes can-make-up.Yes Can make-up
Can make-up in five, four, three, two, one.
Hey, what's that? What is it?
Hey, I really don't like number 7.
Number 7 is also a sprout.
There's really no substance.
This is what I wanted to talk about,
I couldn't think of anything I wanted to talk about,
I'm going to talk about the most unimportant thing of all.
I've been cooking sprouts lately.
Oh, that's good.
Yesterday, too, for bean sprouts,
Mix bean sprouts with various seasonings,
I added potato starch and water,
I made a very tender dish,
I also made Namuro.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
Are you sure he's not here?
But recently, I saw a picture of fried shrimp next to bean sprouts.
It's not fried shrimp. These are bean sprouts.
No, no, no, Yuna-san.
This is bean sprouts.
This is radish.
Thick?
That's not the point.
They are all miserable.
They were all labeled "fried shrimp.
They're bean sprouts.It's bean sprouts.
He said it didn't look like bean sprouts.
It's bean sprouts.
Say cheese ball.
Cheese balls?
I'm talking about cheese balls.
Cheese balls are...
It's a food, too,
Can I say "medium santorio"?
I went to Shin-Okubo.
And there, I had this chicken takkarbi,
Chicken takkarbi.
Like a plate.
We shared a plate full of chicken takkarbi with three other people.
After that, we had
Waffle.
Croffle.
Then we had shaved ice.
It was delicious. That was a happy day.
It was a really happy day.
The cheese ball in it was really good.
It's a cheese ball.
Please wait for the food.
I'm sorry.
I've been eating a lot lately.
Oh, come on.
Let us do the show.
First with us,First with us,
Like 1,2,3 something kinda nice.
It was a live week, right?
Well, you know.
I wish we could have talked.
Well, this time.
This is the end of the survey.
Okay, that's it.
That's all for now.
To be continued,
And so it goes,
A year of fun and fluff.
Yay!
It's been almost a year since Emayama joined Ebichu.
So today we are all together,
I'd like to look back on this happy and wonderful year that has been filled with many things.
It's nice.
It's good. We've already been together for a year, right?
Did you think it was a year early, Yuna? Or did you think it was long?
Did you think it was long?
But really, we have been running through this year since the spring,
I didn't really feel the passage of time that much,
Recently, when I announce my next show or something,
But recently, when I announce my next show or something,
January 2024,
I was so surprised. I'm really surprised.
That's right. That's early. It still feels early to me.
Of course, it was my first time to be a university artist,
And then there were the free live shows with the five of us,
There were so many events,It was really a crazy event,
It really felt like it was a real shun and ran through.
It was a moment, wasn't it?
It was quick.
So today I would like to look back on some memories,
First of all, I would like to ask you, what was the funniest and most humorous thing you ever did? I guess I'd like to ask what was the funniest and most humorous thing that happened to me.
I had a live concert this time,
I'm sure there are things that remain in your memory,
I'd like to talk about some of the things that were a little bit bitter.
What was the funniest thing you ever did?
I recently unearthed one,
I unearthed a voice memo of Nana Yanagina practicing a song at the KAMIS before our debut concert,
When I listened to it, I heard the rap part of "Hot Up",
I was listening to them, and I unearthed the voice memo of her practicing the rap part of "Hot Up" and the part of "Cake Up Anpanmans" very hard,
I'm sure you can all understand that,
I'm sure you can all understand that, but they were practicing hard even though they were repeating the same thing over and over again,
The last part is the swimming part, right?
At the end, there is a part where they are swimming, and both of them were swimming in a very barbed voice.
When I listened to it back, I wondered why they were reading it in such a barbed tone. It was really interesting at the time,
It was really interesting at the time.
I realized it recently.
I took Emma's voice memo,
I asked her what it was about, and she replied, "I don't know. I asked her what it was,
I asked her what it was, and she said, "Hot up, I wanted to practice the hammoly of my first chorus,
I wanted to practice my first chorus, so I asked Yanagina to do the hammoly,
I had saved a lot of the chimera with Emma singing the chimera.
In the process of practicing, I got to that point,
I was saying "webbing" and "idding" a lot,
After that, swimming was really fun.
It was very interesting.It was so much fun.
Sure, and besides,
He was reading it really well,
He was saying "bang bang" really hard,
It was really funny,
And it was really long.
Swimming.
I wonder what it was about.
Have you ever invited Emma to go swimming with you?
I was, very much so,
I remember this every time I go to the beach,
In "Cinderella of the Temporary Contract",
Emma says her first line in Cinderella of the Temporary Contract.
We always do this in our lessons,
We always practice with a wooden stick as a microphone,
I always do,
I always point to the glass mouth of the Hime no Nesic and say, "I'm looking for a pretty girl,
Yuna does it like this.
And I do it like this.
I'm doing it like this.
I'm doing it like this,
Yuna, was this your first time?
Was it the second VTR?
That time,
I'm doing it like this,
I was using a wooden stick,
And the people around us didn't notice,
I was doing it like this, but I was using a wooden stick, and the people around me didn't notice, but we both burst out laughing,
I still get a grin on my face when we play live.
I remember it now.I just remembered.
I said I would never grab Yuna again,
But then I remembered.
I knew that a regular microphone is good because it's black.
Yes, it is.
The dummy mic I always use is no good because the wooden stick is skin-colored.
That's true. It's just like skin.
I was really surprised, wasn't I?
That's true.
Then I grin.
That's right. That was funny.
It's okay that I'm not talking yet. You're grinning.
I'm in the middle of saying my lines,
I'm always trying to hold back really seriously because I'm afraid I'm going to laugh.
I always get funny. I'll remember it.
I do remember, don't I?
Aren't you good at it? With the wooden sticks.
It's scary, isn't it? I was holding the microphone, and they grabbed me with this kind of grip.
I felt a little bit of pain.
When I was holding it.
It was really interesting.
It was really the first time I played Forbidden Karma,
When I played the role of Cinderella from Forbidden Karma,
Ema said, "I'm busy being a princess.
I can't do that.
When I was doing Forbidden Karma, I was using this hand. When I hold the microphone.
Keep talking like this.
I'm busy being a princess.
No. It's no good after Forbidden Karma anymore.
It's no good.It's no good.
It's difficult.
And then Yukari held it down with a shush like this.
Then I realized it and gasped,
I thought it was a little bit funny.
I thought it was a bit funny. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
That was the story behind Yukari de Fu~,
What should I do now?
A story that can be told now.
You mean to each other?
What do you have to say?
I do,
What can we talk about now?
I'm not going to get angry.
I'm not mad at you.
There was a time when we were both staying in the nap room,
Yuna had fallen asleep before taking a bath, so I decided to take a bath first,
I forgot to wash my face,
But I wanted to wash my face,
I found it right in front of me,
I thought, "This is Yuna's face wash,
But..,
I was starting to get a little ahead of myself.
At that time, you were only a few months old.
You couldn't ask him to lend it to you.
And I thought I could use it without saying so,
I didn't have it yet, and I was frustrated about what to do with it,
But I used it.
Yes, I did.Yes, I do.
So you're okay with that kind of stuff?
I also made sure to use a whisk.
Yes, I did. By the way, that whisk is not mine,
It belongs to another person who is staying in the nap room.
It's okay. I'll keep it a secret.
No one used it, but I left it there.
That's what I meant.
So we can do the same thing?
Don't get mad at me.
I can't get mad.
When we stay in the sleeping quarters together,
You buy food from the community, right?
We both bought salads with separate dressings,
Emma bought a sesame dressing?
I bought the Japanese dressing,
I bought the Japanese dressing, but once I put it in the fridge, I forgot about it,
I put the sesame dressing on my own salad.
I put the sesame dressing on my own salad, and she said she might have forgotten to buy the sesame dressing,
I said, "I did buy it, didn't I? I said, "You did buy it, didn't you? I said something like, "You bought it, didn't you?
I ate my salad as usual.
The next time I looked in the fridge, I found my own salad dressing in there,
I ate Ema's dressing without permission.
I remember this quite well,
We both bought salads,
And we both bought different kinds,
I didn't notice it, and Emma didn't notice it either,
I also didn't notice that we were eating gomadoreh,
I didn't really have it, and I thought it was too raw to eat,
I thought I could eat them raw, but I think I did.I think I ate it.
I was eating a tasteless salad,
I was saying, "You poor thing.
I said, "You poor thing,
I was eating it myself.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
We have each other.
Yes, we do.
Yes, we did.
I can say that around here now,
I can tell you when it happened,
I had been with him for only a few months,
I couldn't be aggressive yet,
So, I'm sorry.
I couldn't say it.
I was afraid of what they would think.
When I came back, I just said, "Normal,
I'm sorry.
My dress got soaked. I would say I was sorry,
But I couldn't say it then.
Yes, that's right.
So you guys have become good friends over the past year.
That's right. Yuna often says that,
I think I was able to get along with Yuna during that period of time,
But looking back now, there are times when I think we were totally distant.
How did the distance between you become closer?
What?
I wonder.
It was a gradual process.It's something gradual.
I wonder what it is.
I wonder what triggered it.
Isn't it the spring tour?
Oh, I see.
The preparation period for the spring tour.
When was the last time we really consulted with each other about Gatchi?
Consultations?
What? No?
When was the last time we talked to each other?
But, you know, we must have talked about it when we were staying in the paper room.
At the time, I thought it was just a secret,
But I think it was Oster.
I wonder.
What is it? I wonder.
It's probably freelove or something.
Freelove?
It could certainly be Mitsubishi free love.
We often worked together and spent a lot of time together, so we often took lessons together,
So it became natural for us to share our love with each other.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
At that time.
We both did. I used Yuna-san's face wash without permission.
I'm sorry.
Which member has made the biggest impression on you since you joined?
Gah!Gah!
The most together one?
Everyone has changed, though,
Yeah, I guess so.
We were all scared, weren't we? At first.
I was so nervous during the audition,
I was really scared,
But I'm not afraid now,
Who are they?
But still..,
Oh, uh..,
Ogura-chan might have been scary.
She was scary.
I was afraid of her because she was a "made yankee,
I was scared,
But now she pulls me along,
She's like a really kind and gentle big sister.
She came in like a crowd,
They came in like that.
It was scary.
And they were doing the waltz part of Cinderella's waltz, when I was the most confused.
I thought, "What am I going to do?
I couldn't do it.
I thought, "What is this movement?
I was stuck, and then it came in.
What's with the snapping?
You can see it in the mirror.
So, at first, avoid eye contact.
What? Even now?What? Even now?
The other two guys in the same group,
What? You're not in it? Like, "Oh, no, I'm not in.
Yes, I'm in. They were like, "Oh, yeah, we're in.
I can't see it, I can't see it, I can't see it.
I couldn't look at it for a long time.
And it was like that. I thought if I saw it, people would think I was skipping practice,
I didn't think about it.
Why are you looking at me? Like, "Why are you looking at me?
That's great,
You were scared because you had never talked before you joined.
Yes, that's right.
I'm busy, and you come in.
You don't think that, do you?
No, no.
Confusion. No, no, no.
When you're confused,
I came in like this,
I see.
I was very nervous.
Well, I remember that.
I remember.
I was so nervous.
What was it?
The first time we did a showroom at Ema/Yuna,
We talked about what we wanted to do.
That's when Ema sat on Aya's lap,
Yuna hugged Riko,Yuna hugged Riko,
I achieved it.
I hugged Riko.
That's what I thought.
Sitting on her lap,
What?
It's not something I do every day.
At the time, she said it was nice,
But then I thought about it.
When do you sit?
Hugs,
For example, when you want to take a picture,
Before a concert, for example,
There are many situations,
When do you sit on my lap?
When Aya is sitting on my lap,
I sit on her lap when she is sitting normally.
What? What? What? That's because you're like, "What?
That was a mistake.
I said I wanted to do it.
Hugging, holding hands, that kind of thing,
I would have been totally fine if it was something like hugging or holding hands or something,
But sitting on his lap?
That's a very high hurdle.
Sitting on the senior member's lap.
Even the older members had never done it before.
You have to make a mistake on purpose.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's also rude.
Try sitting on purpose.Sit down on purpose.
Well, Yuna, when and at what time?
It was pretty soon.
Already, the first time I spread out,
I got a hug when I was kinky.
That's nice.
Okay, I'll leave a comment.
I don't know. Shall we try it?
The chair froze.
Chair?
Chair stuck.
Aya, I thought it was a chair.
Are you sure?
That's so rude.
I'm going to get super mad at you. That's as expected.
Oh no.
They said it's because you're handsome.
That's right.
Did he say that?
He told me he's a good-looking guy.
That's so sweet.
He's so kind.
That's nice.
He hugs me a lot, doesn't he?
He does, doesn't he?
New goal?
I guess it's a new goal.
But no thanks,
Are you getting to know them well?
We are getting to know each other well, aren't we?We are getting to know each other in many ways.
More than a year ago.
Because we went out to dinner.
And what else?
We hugged.
I knew it,
I think it was a knee hug.
What? How do you sit? I don't know.
But..,
Yuno, Cocona, and Nonoka, and Konoya and Nonoka, they can do it.
Yes, they can do it.
It's just a matter of how we get into it.
Just with a groove.
Like sitting down.
I see.
Yuno-chan sits down, you know.
She makes me sit down.
That's right.
Hmm.
What were they all looking at?
I wonder. Oh, there's this one.
Wow.
They say it's good for beauty.
That's true.
Sitting on top of Aya is good for your beauty.
So it's good for beauty.
Indeed. Then it might be a good idea.
Tell her that you have to do it as a project in the showroom,
On the contrary.
I have to do it.I have to do it.
I have to sit down for a minute, please.
That's it.
You're not going to sit down?
That's what I mean.
That's good, too. That's true.
That's for sure.
I'll surprise him or something.
Certainly.
Ah! Tachikurami.
That's funny.
Indeed.
Is it a success that you do it?
I feel like I'm forcing myself to sit up hard.
Somehow.
Please do your best.
I'll do my best.
Yes, I will.
What? Well then...
Okay.
Soon.
You two will be one year old on October 1st.
That's right,
Thank you very much for one year.
Thank you very much. Thank you for all your support.
It really feels like a year has already come to an end,
Yesterday, when we were meeting up,
I wanted to stamp a "hello" to you when I met up with you yesterday,I wanted to put a stamp of "Best regards" but I mistakenly put a stamp of "See you next year",
But I mistakenly put a "hello again next year" stamp on it.
It was too soon.
It's already fallen out of my mind.
I have a little more time left.
I will do my best in the second year, so please give me your best.
That's all for now.
Now, if you want to go one step further,
I would like to go to the ending.
Yes, I will.
So, this is Yukari de Yukari de Don't Tread on Shrimps!
Showroom No. 61 is ending in the blink of an eye.
It's early, isn't it?
So, I would like to make an announcement here.
Yes.
There will be a private Ebistu Gaku Okera Disco 2023 on Saturday, October 7, 2023 at Hoshihiko Yokohama National Grand Hall.
And on Sunday, October 22nd, it will be held at Tokyo International Forum Hall A,
Tickets are still on sale, so please come out and join us.
Please come.
Sounds interesting, right?
I made a mistake.
And next,
Private Evistu Gaku Akita Bunko. What Changes and What Remains the Same will be held on Saturday, November 11 at the Akita Performing Arts Center Milhous Main Hall.
Please come, everyone, as it will definitely be fun.
And one more thing.
One more thing.
An important announcement.
Ebisu Junior High School New Year's Grand Performance 2024, "The Dragon that Flies High and Beyond" will be held on January 6 and 7, 2024 at Pearly MM.
I really wrote about it, but it will definitely be fun, so please come and play.I really wrote about it, but it will definitely be fun, so please come and visit.
We'll be waiting.
And check out the top 5 final rankings.
Ah!
I'm out.
Oh, I can see this way.
My eyes are bad.
Thank you, 5th place, Shackel survive.
Thank you, 4th place, ON.
Fujisasa.
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Cute.
Third place, thank you, Baribari.
Second place, late тот saúl, thank you.
things am fussing.
I read it wrong.
I am really sorry.
Thank you very much.
So this is the 61st installment of Ebitune's first fussing showroom.
The next transmission will be announced as soon as it is decided.
There will be no review session after this distribution.
There won't be.
No, there will not be. Is there?
No, there will not be.
Oh, thank goodness.
Thank you for being a one-member impossible.
You're really getting good at this.You are really getting good at this.
Wow!
Happy Birthday!
That's all for now.
This is Sherizu Ebichu BAKURA.
Bye bye.
This video is by traditional traditional Japanese culture,
by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
By traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,By traditional traditional culture,
By traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
By traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,By traditional traditional culture,
By traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,
by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture. by traditional traditional culture,